(Leonard(on screen):)I can't help but remember
(Leonard(on screen):)the last time
I was in this auditorium.
(Leonard(on screen):)Two guys from the lacrosse team
(Leonard(on screen):)played keep-away
with my asthma inhaler.
(Leonard(on screen):)But enough about
my ten-year reunion.
(Leonard(on screen):)I'd also like
to take a moment
(Leonard(on screen):)to thank
my beautiful fiancée
(Leonard(on screen):)for to helping make
this speech possible,
(Leonard(on screen):)even though weather
nearly prevented it.
(Penny:)Oh. Hello.
I-I didn't know
he was gonna point it at me,
(Penny:)so... don't do drugs
and stay in school.
(Leonard:)They're graduating.
Okay, bye!
(Howard:)All right, the power
supply is reconnected.
(Howard:)I think we're
back in business.
(Howard:)Let's just run a few tests
before we take it outside.
(Howard:)Sheldon, we got WiFi?
Check.
(Howard:)GPS?
(Howard:)Battery charged?
Check.
(Bernadette:)Four hours of our lives gone?
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Howard:)All systems go.
(Howard:)In five...
(Together:)...four, three, two, one.
(electrical crackle)